<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

	<channel>
		<title>US EPA Climate and Energy Resources for State, Local and Tribal Governments</title>
		<link>https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate</link>
		<atom:link href="https://www.epa.gov/sites/production/files/2016-06/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<description>This feed provides news and updates regarding EPA&apos;s Climate and Energy Resources for State, Local and Tribal Governments.</description>




<item>
      <title>January 18 – Additional Proven Program Profiles on Energy Efficiency and Renewable Energy in Low-Income Communities Now Available from EPA</title>
      <link>https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/bringing-benefits-energy-efficiency-and-renewable-energy-low-income-communities?&amp;utm_medium=rss</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>EPA's State and Local Climate and Energy Program is developing a series of <a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/bringing-benefits-energy-efficiency-and-renewable-energy-low-income-communities">case studies and program profiles</a> to help officials in state and local energy, environmental, housing, and social services agencies, non-profits, and utilities understand promising practices and successful models that they can use to reduce greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions by bringing energy efficiency and renewable energy (EE/RE) to low-income communities.</p><p>The <a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/bringing-benefits-energy-efficiency-and-renewable-energy-low-income-communities#Case Studies and Program Profiles">profiles in this ongoing series</a> highlight effective programs at the state and local levels that have led to the successful adoption of EE/RE in low-income communities. The profiles focus on how these programs have addressed, in a practical manner, the challenges to ensuring low-income households share in the multiple benefits of EE/RE. </p><p>The following program profiles have just been added: </p><ul><li><a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/duke-energy-neighborhood-energy-saver-program">Duke Energy: Neighborhood Energy Saver Program</a></li><li><a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/duluth-flood-recovery-program">Duluth Flood Recovery Program</a></li><li><a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/elevate-energy-energy-efficiency-services-affordable-multifamily-buildings">Elevate Energy: Energy Efficiency Services for Affordable Multifamily Buildings</a></li></ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 January 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>




<item>
      <title>January 17 – Updated State Greenhouse Gas Inventory Tool modules now available!</title>
      <link>https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/download-state-inventory-and-projection-tool?&amp;utm_medium=rss</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to announce the release of <a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/download-state-inventory-and-projection-tool?&amp;utm_medium=rss">new State Greenhouse Gas Inventory Tool modules</a>! In this update, all modules were updated with activity data from 1990 through 2014, wherever possible. The Projection Tool and the accompanying Energy Consumption Projection Tool have also been updated with projections currently starting at 2015. The Projection tool allows users to create a simple forecast of all emissions through 2030, based on historical emissions from the 1990-2014 timeframe.</p><p>The updated modules are now available through the EPA website at: <a href="https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/download-state-inventory-and-projection-tool?&amp;utm_medium=rss">https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/download-state-inventory-and-projection-tool</a></p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 January 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
      <title>June 6 – Webcast recordings available for "Solar for All: Making it Happen in Low-Income Communities" webcast.</title>
      <link>https://www.epa.gov/statelocalclimate/solar-all-making-it-happen-low-income-communities-0?&amp;utm_medium=rss</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>In April 2016, EPA hosted a webinar providing a nationwide overview of community solar (shared solar) and rooftop solar programs available to low-income households. This webinar featured case study discussions by solar energy policy experts to illustrate the opportunities, challenges, and benefits of providing low-income households access to solar energy.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 6 June 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>



	</channel>
</rss>