<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

	<channel>
		<title>US EPA Clean Power Plan Toolbox</title>
		<link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox</link>
		<atom:link href="http://www2.epa.gov/sites/production/files/2014-09/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<description>This feed provides news and updates regarding EPA&apos;s Clean Power Plan Toolbox.</description>


<item>
      <title>February 23 – Proceeding available from January, 2016 webcasts.</title>
      <link>http://www.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-clean-power-plan-webinars</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p><On January 14, 2016, EPA hosted a webinar to discuss how energy efficiency can be used as a compliance measure in the Clean Power Plan, and what the rule says about EM&V. A <a href="http://www.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-clean-power-plan-webinars">recording</a> of this webcast is now available.</p><p>On January 11, 2016, EPA hosted a webinar to provide a basic overview of emissions trading, an explanation of common terms (including budgets, set-asides, etc.), a general description of how mass-based and rate-based trading works, and a discussion of tools and resources. A <a href="http://www.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-clean-power-plan-webinars">recording</a> of this webcast is now available.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 February 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
      <title>October 21 – Opportunity to provide feedback on the Clean Energy Incentive Program (CEIP)</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/ceip-next-steps</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/ceip-next-steps">The Clean Energy Incentive Program (CEIP) Next Steps</a> document details the EPA’s outreach strategy for stakeholder input on the design and implementation of the CEIP. The document also lists several CEIP provisions about which the EPA is seeking stakeholder input.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 October 2015 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>



    
      <item>
      <title>August 4 - Join CPP Overview Webinar today at 2 PM EDT</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplan/clean-power-plan-overview-webinar</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>To learn more and register, visit: <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplan/clean-power-plan-overview-webinar">http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplan/clean-power-plan-overview-webinar</a> </p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 4 August 2015 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 3 - New and updated resources added to Clean Power Plan Toolbox for States website</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-webinar-series-proposed-clean-power-plan</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>Visit the <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox">Clean Power Plan Toolbox for States</a> to access state-specific fact sheets, an updated CPP State Goal Visualizer, State Plan Decision Tree, Technical Summary fact sheet, and draft Evaluation, Measurement and Verification Guidance (now open for public input), and EPA’s Clean Power Plan Training Curriculum.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 3 August 2015 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
      
      
    <item>
      <title>Join April 2 webinar for communities on Section 111(d) of the Clean Air Act</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-webinar-series-proposed-clean-power-plan</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>EPA invites communities to participate in an April 2 webinar that will provide an overview of the Clean Air Act, with a specific focus on section 111(d) and the state plan structure under section 111(d). The goal of this webinar is to provide communities with background information on the authorities that EPA is using to implement the Clean Power Plan. For more information on the Clean Power Plan, please visit: <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/clean-power-plan-proposed-rule">http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/clean-power-plan-proposed-rule.</a></p><p><b>Date</b>: Thursday, April 2, 2015 <br/><b>Time</b>: 2:00 pm-3:00 pm (EDT)<br/><b>Meeting Link</b>: <a href="https://epa.connectsolutions.com/cpp-community500/">https://epa.connectsolutions.com/cpp-community500/</a><br/><b>Participant Number</b>:  1-800-309-5450<br/><b>Conference ID</b>: 7490460</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 March 2015 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>


    <item>
      <title>March 4 – Listen to webinar on Clean Power Plan implementation</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-webinar-series-proposed-clean-power-plan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On February 24, 2015, EPA hosted a  webinar for states, tribes and territories that provided  an update on information about implementing the Clean Power Plan. The webinar  offers states and tribes an early look at EPA&rsquo;s preliminary thinking on tools  it plans to develop to assist states, tribes and territories with implementing  the Clean Power Plan. All presentations and recordings from these webinars are <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-webinar-series-proposed-clean-power-plan">now  available online</a>.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 4 March 2015 3:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
	
	<item>
      <title>November 21 – Listen to Webinars on the Clean Power Plan Proposed Rule's Notice of Data Availability and the Supplemental Proposal</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-webinar-series-proposed-clean-power-plan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On November 5, 2014 EPA hosted two webinars: one describing the Clean Power Plan Proposed Rule <a href="https://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/clean-power-plan-proposed-rule-notice-data-availability">Notice of Data Availability</a>, and the other describing the <a href="https://wcms.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/clean-power-plan-supplemental-proposal">Clean Power Plan Supplemental Proposal</a> to address carbon pollution from affected power plants in Indian Country and U.S. territories. These webinars are designed for technical staff from Tribes, states, local governments and territories and offer a detailed presentation about the respective action. All presentations and recordings from these webinars are <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/epa-webinar-series-proposed-clean-power-plan">now available online</a>.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 November 2014 1:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>October 28 – EPA requests comment, hosts webinars on additional Clean Power Plan information and proposes carbon goals for Indian Country and U.S. Territories</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/how-comment-clean-power-plan-proposed-rule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>As part of the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency’s extensive outreach since issuing the proposed <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards">Clean Power Plan</a>, EPA is making additional information and ideas available for public comment in a notice of data availability (NODA). At the same time, EPA is following through on its commitment made in June to propose goals to reduce carbon pollution in areas of Indian Country and U.S. Territories where fossil-fuel power plants are located.</p><p>In issuing today’s NODA, EPA is seeking to ensure that all interested parties are aware of the issues and ideas that have been consistently raised by a diverse group of stakeholders, so that everyone has the opportunity to consider them as they formulate their comments, which are due on Dec. 1, 2014. Notices of data availability are commonly used to present additional information for the public to consider. They do not change a proposal, nor are they a complete summary of the wide variety of ideas that have been raised. They allow EPA to continue seeking ideas and comments on these and many other issues as the agency works toward a final rule that is flexible and empowers states to chart their own, customized path to meet goals for reducing harmful carbon pollution.</p><p>In a separate but related action, EPA is proposing goals for areas of Indian Country and U.S. Territories where fossil fuel-fired power plants are located to reduce their carbon pollution by 2030. Proposed goals for these areas were not included in the June 2014 proposed Clean Power Plan. The supplemental proposal relies on the approach used in the June 2014 Clean Power Plan and is based on new information and data provided through additional outreach to covered facilities and tribal and territorial governments. The proposal outlines a diverse range of options that tribes and territories could use to meet their goals. EPA will hold a public hearing on the supplemental proposal on Nov. 19, 2014 in Phoenix, Ariz. and will accept comment through Dec. 19, 2014.</p><p>Fact sheets and details about the NODA and the supplemental proposal: <a href="http://www.epa.gov/cleanpowerplan">http://www.epa.gov/cleanpowerplan</a></p><p>EPA is hosting webinars about both the <a href="https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/7303652584663466241">NODA</a> and the <a href="https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/4241469820353838081">supplemental proposal</a> on Wednesday, November 5.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 October 2014 1:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>    

    <item>
      <title>Clean Power Plan Comment Period Extended </title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/how-comment-clean-power-plan-proposed-rule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The comment period for the Clean Power Plan Proposed Rule has been extended by 45 days. Comments must now be received by December 1, 2014. Learn more about how to comment at <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/how-comment-clean-power-plan-proposed-rule">http://www2.epa.gov/carbon-pollution-standards/how-comment-clean-power-plan-proposed-rule</a>.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 September 2014 1:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Clean Power Plan State Goal Visualizer Now Available</title>
      <link>http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/clean-power-plan-documents-and-resources</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In the proposed Clean Power Plan (CPP), the EPA sets individual pollution-to-power goal rates for states to meet in 2030 by applying four "building blocks." This <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/clean-power-plan-documents-and-resources">interactive, excel-based tool</a> presents that goal rate calculation for each state in a step-wise and graphical format, using the same steps as described in the proposal and the state goal computation technical support document. It presents data that is already available on the CPP website and in the proposed rule docket, and the calculations are the same as those that are in the state goal computation technical support document and its supporting data files. The Visualizer is available at <a href="http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/clean-power-plan-documents-and-resources">http://www2.epa.gov/cleanpowerplantoolbox/clean-power-plan-documents-and-resources</a>.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 September 2014 1:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    

	</channel>
</rss>